Guide to the BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
- Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
  - Code no.2103: Auburn Shoe Manufacturers Association and Lewiston Auburn Shoeworkers Protective Association, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2112: J.F. McElwain Co. and Hew Hampshire Shoe Workers Union, 1959-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2114: Southern California Shoe Manufacturers Association and United Shoe Workers of America, Local 122, AFL-CIO, 1959- 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2116: Weyenberg Shoe Manufacturing Company and Boot and Shoe Workers Union, Locals 721, 651, 379, 170, AFL-CIO, 1973- 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2117: Fulton County Glove Manufacturers, Inc. and United Glove Workers of America, Operators and Day Hands Branch, 1957- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2124-1: Ladies Shoe Industry and Joint Council No. 13, United Shoe Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2124-2: Ladies Shoe Industry and Joint Council No. 13, United Shoe Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Code no.2124-3: Ladies Shoe Industry and Joint Council No. 13, United Shoe Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968-1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.1201-1: Boise Cascade Corporations and International Woodworkers of America, International Falls Local 4-33, 1957-1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Code no.1201-1: Minnesota and Ontario Paper Company and International Woodworkers of America, International Falls Local 4-33, 1959- 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.1210: Gulf States Paper Association and United Paper workers International Union, Local 157 and 297, AFL-CIO, 1974- 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Code no.1223: Northwest Paper Company and United Papermakers and Paper workers, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, AFL-CIO, 1952-1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Code no.1249: Bay Area Multiple-West Coast Paper and Paper Converting Industry and Printing Specialties and Paper Products Unions Nos. 362, 380, 382, 387, 388, 612, 626, 659, 678, 696, 706, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.1254-1: Packaging Corporation of America, Rittman, Ohio Plant and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 150, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Code no.1254-2: Packaging Corporation of America, Rittman, Ohio Plant and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local 150, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Code no.1257: Bowaters Southern Paper Corporation and United Paper workers International Union and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Code no.1258: Inland Container Corporation and United Paper workers International Union, Locals 31, 114, 1046, 4658, 1737, 954, 200, 1029, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Code no.1436: Twin City Commercial Printers and Bookbinders and Bindery Women, Twin City Local 12, International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1961-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1456: Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York and Graphic Arts International Union, Local 43-B, 1974- 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Code no.1601: Industrial Chemicals Division, Allied Chemical Corporation, Syracuse Works and United Steelworkers of America, Local 12457, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Code no.1602: American Cynamid Company, Bound Book Plant and International Chemical Workers Union, 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Code no.1603: Diamond Shamrock Corporation, Painesville Works and United Steelworkers of America, Local 12231, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Code no.1612: Monsanto Company, John F. Queeny Plant, St. Louis, Mo. and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 16, 1960- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Code no.1625: FMC Corporation, Chemical Group, Film and Packaging Division, Fredericksburg Plant and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Local 713, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1659: Buffalo Dye Plant of Specialty Chemicals Division, Allied Chemical Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 12330, 1967-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1667-2: Miles Laboratories, Inc. and International Union of District 50 Allied and Technical Workers of the US and Canada, Local 12273, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Code no.1900-1: Armstrong Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1973- 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Code no.1903: Firestone Tire and Rubber Company and International Union of United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Code no.1904: General Motors Corporation, Inland Division and International Union of United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 87, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Code no.1906: B.F. Goodrich Company and International Union of United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 5, 715, 241, 351, 318, 281, 1967-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Code no.1908: Goodyear Tire and rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 2, 12, 131, 185, 200, 286, 289, 290, 307, 532, 831, 835, 843, 878, 904, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1910: Mansfield Tire and Rubber Company and Local 17, United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1973- 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Code no.1912-1: Uniroyal, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Code no.1912-2: Uniroyal, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Code no.1912-3: Uniroyal, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Code no.1925-1: Foster Grant Co., Inc. and Local Union 60, affiliated with Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, 1959- 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Code no.1925-2: Foster Grant Co., Inc. and Local Union 60, affiliated with Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, 1969- 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2319: T.C. Wheaton Co. and Wheaton Glass Company and Glass Bottle Blowers Association of US and Canada, AFL-CIO, Local 219, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2328-1: Chinaware Companies and International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, AFL-CIO, 1959-1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Code no.2329: Stetson China Company and Local Union 116, International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, AFL-CIO, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2332: Carborundum Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO and Abrasive Workers Local 8-12058, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2330: United States Potters Association and International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, AFL-CIO, 1957-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2342: Illuminating and Allied Glassware Manufacturers Association and American Flint Glassworkers Union, AFL-CIO, 1974- 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2345-1: American Standard, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pottery and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, Locals 175, 26, 89, 301, 220, 7, 218, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2352-2: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 12, 378, 33, 50.80.164, 176, 200, 313, 532, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2354: General Portland, Inc. and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2366-3: Medusa Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 173, 480, 23, 81, 34, 175, 179, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4417: E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company and International Chemical Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 257, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8302: Republic Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8303-1: Tennessee Coal and Iron Division of United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960- 1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8303-2: Tennessee Coal and Iron Division of United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962- 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8304: Anaconda Company and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Butte Miners' Union No. 1, 1960- 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8305: Calumet Division of Calumet & Hecla, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8307: Phelps Dodge Corporation and Douglas Metal Trades Council, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8315: Humble Oil and Refining Co. and Employees' Federation of the Humble Oil and Refining Co., 1953-1956 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8317: Barre District, Granite Manufacturers of Montpelier, Barre, Northfield and Vicinity and United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, AFL-CIO, locals 8, 11, 14, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2324 / 591193: General Refractories Company and International Union of, District 50; United Mine Workers of America, Local 14702, 1966-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1817 / 591240: Standard Oil Company of California, Western Operations, Inc. and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1-561, 1961-1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Code no.1651 / 591337: Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company, Port Ivory Factory and Independent Oil and Chemical Workers, 1960- 1968 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.2577-2: Anaconda Company and United Steelworkers of America; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers; International Union of Operating Engineers; Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International; International, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2579-2: Anaconda Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6002, 1968-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2579-1: Anaconda Company and United Steelworkers of America, re: Working Conditions and Wages, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Code no.2912-1: American Standard, Inc. and Standard Allied Trades Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Atlanta Georgia and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Elizabeth, New Jersey and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Kansas City, Kansas and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Dallas, Texas and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Medford, Mass. and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Code no.1103-6: Simmons Company, Munster, Indiana and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1973- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.1123-1: Ward Furniture Manufacturing, Division of Desoto and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 281, AFL-CIO, 1970- 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Code no.1124-1: Schnadig Corporation and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Code no.2502-2: Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2508-2: Babcock and Wilcox Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1082, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2527: Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2567-1: Lynchburg Foundry Co. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 2556, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2567-2: Lynchburg Foundry Co. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 2556, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2612-3: Reynolds Metals Company and Aluminum Workers International Union, 1965-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Code no.2613-4: Western Electric Company and Communication Equipment Workers, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2614-3: Doehler Jarvis Division of National Lead Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 1056, 1057, 1053, 257, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Code no.2626-1: Belle City Malleable Iron Company and Racine Steel Castings Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 1056, 1057, 1053, 257, 1964-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2661: Western Electric, Buffalo Plant and Communications Workers of America, Local 1162, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2668-1: Western Electric, Atlanta Works and Communications Workers of America, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Code no.2912-2: American Standard, Inc. and Local Lodge No. 1390, affiliated with District Lodge No. 27, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2935-1: Structural Steel and Ornamental Iron Association of N.J., Inc. and Shopmen's Local Union 545 of International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, AFL- CIO, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2698: Amerace-Esna Corporation (Elastic Stop Nut Division) and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 726, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2985: Chrysler Corporation, Airtemp Kentucky Plant and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1684, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2986: Kaiser Steel Corporation, Metal Products Division, Napa, California and Machinists Automotive Trades District Lodge 190 of Northern California, 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3225-1: International Harvester Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3225-2: International Harvester Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1968-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3226: International Harvester Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3255: Sundstrand Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 592, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3265-1: USM Corporation, Beverly Manufacturing Division and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1975- 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3266-1: Whitin Machine Works, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3284-2: National Cash Register Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1616, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3297: Hussmann Refrigerator Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 13889, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3355-2: Xerox and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge 720, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    1973-1974, 1977-1978
  - Code no.3372-1: Joy Manufacturing Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1842, 1968- 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Code no.3628-1: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, 1960- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Code no.3649-2: Admiral Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1031, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Code no.3660: RCA Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Locals 1907, 1160, 1048, 1424, 2237, 1710, 1048, 1906, 1666, 1207, 2105, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Code no.3676: Western Electric and Communications Workers of America, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Code no.3677-4: Teletype Corporation and Teletype Employees' Industrial Union, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3677: Teletype Corporation and Teletype Employees' Industrial Union, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3681: Western Electric, Montgomery Plant and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local1942, 1974- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3683-1: Western Electric, Oklahoma City Works and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2021, 1974- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3684-1: Western Electric, Merrimack Valley Works and Communications Workers of America, Local 1365, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3686: Western Electric, Allentown Works and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1522, 1974- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3687: Western Electric, Hawthorne Works and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1859, 1974- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3694: RCA Corporation and Radio Communications Assemblers Union, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3760-3: Teletype Corporation, Little Rock, Arkansas and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2022, 1974- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3760-3: Teletype Corporation, Little Rock, Arkansas and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2022, 1971- 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3784: Bendix Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Sidney Lodge No. 1529, 1971- 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3788: Zenith Radio Corporation of Iowa and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Victory Lodge No. 1637, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3792: General Electric Company, Milwaukee Plant and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3797-2: Western Electric Company, Northern Illinois Works and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2310, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Code no.4004-3: Bendix Corporation, Bendix-Westinghouse Air Brake Division and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 971, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Code no.4001-1: Chrysler Corporation, Airtemp Kentucky Plant and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Code no.4017-4: Eaton Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 196, 220, 625, 407, 302, 1611, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Code no.4019: Ford Motor Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 196, 220, 625, 407, 302, 1611, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4022-1: General Motors Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4025-2: Kelsey-Hayes Company and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 670, 1964- 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Code no.4028-1: Mack Trucks and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 68, 677, 76, 229, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4028-2: Mack Trucks and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 171, 68, 76, 229, 677, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4036-4: North American Rockwell Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 274, 437, 291, 1568, 709, 174, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4102-1: Dravo Corporation and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Code no.4111: Pacific Coast Shipbuilding and Ship Repair Firms and Metal Trades Department of the AFL-CIO, 1962-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Code no.4112: Employers Engaged in Shipbuilding and Repair, Boatbuilding and Repair and Allied Industries and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 1149, 3116, 266, 1020, 470, 1136, 2071, 562, 1272, 1184, 1532, 2084, 159, 1959-1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Code no.4126: Diamond Reo Trucks, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 650, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Code no.4188: Marathon Letourneau Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Code no.4189: Seatrain Shipbuilding Corp. and United Industrial Workers of the Seafarers International Union of North America, 1974- 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Code no.4402: Kollsman Instrument Company and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, District 15, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Code no.4426-1: Warminster Fiberglass Company and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8308: White Pine Copper Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8309: Bunker Hill Company and Northwest Metal Workers Union, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8322: Inspiration Consolidated Copper Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1967-1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8503: Furnace Dealers and Sheet Metal Contractors of Northern California and Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, Local 216, 1960-1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Code no.4429 / 590730: Lear Siegler, Inc., Grand Rapids Plant Instrumental Division and International United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 330, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4071 / 591115: Aircraft-Missiles Division of Fairchild Stratos Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 842, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Code no.591334: Sealed Power Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 637, 1958-1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Code no.4132 / 591351: American Bosch Arma Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 206, 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Code no.591361: Planing Mills and Cabinetwork Firms in San Francisco Bay Counties and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Millmen's Union Locals 550 and 1956, 1959-1967 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Code no.591597: Pattern Makers' League of North America and Pattern Makers' Association of Detroit and Vicinity, AFL-CIO, 1964- 1970 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2939 / 590267: National Screw and Manufacturing Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 8433, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Code no.4051: Bendix Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Code no.4056: Boeing Company and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1963-1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)